Okay, so over here in the left,
好 在界面左边
we have the file picker and it gives you a few options
我们有文件选取器 它给你的一些选择和特征
and features to help manage the files in your project.
会帮助你管理项目中的文件
So say for example if I want to open up the read me mark down,
比如 我想要打开 README.md 文件
I'll just double click on it and opens up right over here on the right side.
我只要双击它 它就会显示在右侧
If you want to add any of your own files,
如果你想要添加自己任意的文件
let's say if you had any existing code or you want to
比如说 你已经有现成的代码 或者 你想要
upload individual folders or files into this project,
在项目中上传个人文件夹 或文件
just go over at the bottom, upload files in
只需要到这里底部 上传文件
history and pick your individual files or folders to add.
或选择你的个人文件或文件夹进行添加
So, just where you do it.
演示一下 就像这样
At the very top, if you wanted to add new files or add new folders into this project,
在顶部 如果你想要在项目中添加新的文件或文件夹
let's go ahead and click on these buttons.
可以点击这些按钮
Here's the one for add file, and here's one for add folder.
这一按钮可以上传文件 这一按钮可以上传文件夹
Click on that, click folder name and create folder.
点击 输入文件夹名字 并创建文件夹
Great. So all the files open up
好的 现在所有的文件都在这一顶部栏展开
over here at the very top, you can go ahead and close them.
你也可以像这样 关闭它们
So over here at the bottom, we have the area for your terminals.
在这一区 是你的终端区
So for this project in particular,
特别是为了这一项目
keep in mind that we have two servers open for this project.
我们准备了两个服务器
So let's check back in the read me over here.
我们再来看看 README 文件
Open up that, and you can see here is that we have one for API server,
打开它 你可以看到我们有一个终端是为了 API 服务器
and another terminal for our pre-scaffold Create React App project.
而另一个终端是为了我们的 pre-scaffold Create React App 项目
So let's go ahead and open up these terminals.
我们可以打开这些终端
Click the plus sign, one for each.
点击这个 “+” 符号 一次打开一个终端
So one thing to note is that for both of these two terminals,
注意一点 对于这两个终端
you're starting at home/workspace,
你是在 home/workspace 这里开始的
but for the API server it lives in the API server folder.
不过 API 服务器存在于 API 服务器文件夹
And for the project,
对于项目来说
it lives inside the frontend folder.
它存在于前端文件夹中
So let's say for example on the API server you would need to
举例来说 在 API 服务器上 你需要用 CD 直接进入那里
CD directly into that, so CD API-server.
也就是输入 cd api-server
The terminal.
这个终端
Make sure you go to the frontend folder,
确保你进入前端文件夹
CD right into it. CD frontend, cool.
输入 cd frontend
And from there, go ahead and install and start your servers.
然后 可以安装并启动你的服务器
So let's go ahead and check out the preview tab on the bottom left.
我们先来检查一下左下角的预览标签
So click on it, and obviously nothing's really happening right now.
点击一下 目前显示出来的是空白状态
We don't actually have any servers open right now.
实际上 我们目前还没有打开任何服务器
So nothing should be running.
所以没有东西在运行
You should be seeing this.
你应该见过这一页面了
But if you actually went ahead and let's say
不过 如果你提前一步 假设
for this project terminal over here, do NPM install.
在该项目终端这里 输入 npm install
Now let's go ahead install the API server.
现在我们继续安装 API 服务器
Great. Now we'll start the server,
好了  现在我们启动服务器
and let's also make sure that we start the project.
也确保我们启动了项目
Great. Now at this point,
很好 现在
if we hit the open preview tab,
如果我们点击预览标签
you should see everything up and running.
你可以看到运行状态
Cool. Good to go.
很棒 我们继续
Now, once you're done with your project,
如果你完成了项目
go here at the very bottom,
可以到页面底部
where you see submit project,
这里有提交项目 (submit project) 按钮
and that's how you get to submit your project for your reviewers to review.
你可以在此提交项目 让审阅导师审阅
One more thing to note, is this menu button over here.
另一点要注意 在菜单按钮这里
So let's say things are running kind of wonky,
如果运行出现问题
need to refresh your workspace,
你可以刷新工作区
but you also want to keep your data.
但你也想要保存数据
In that case, you click on refresh workspace.
在这种情况下 你可以点击 REFRESH WORKSPACE （刷新工作区）
But let's say if you want to restart everything,
如果你想要从头开始
bring it back to the original state,
恢复工作区初始状态
bring back all the starter code that you first began with, 00:02:56,970 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 you can actually do so by hitting reset data.最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6
恢复一开始的起始代码 00:02:56,970 --&gt; 00:00:00,000 你可以点击 RESET DATA （重置数据）